<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string name="start_direction">Swipe Left for more information</string>
    <string name="middle_direction">Swipe Left for more information, Right to go back</string>
    <string name="end_direction">Swipe Right to go back</string>

    <string name="what_is_it">"
        AutoResponder is an application that automatically replies to incoming SMS and MMS messages for you!

        This allows you to not be constantly replying to messages if you are driving, at the gym, at work, or would rather not be bothered!

        To enable this, simply toggle the main switch to ON, and the app will answer messages for you! This status is displayed in the Notification Drawer.

        For a complete experience, please enable all Permissions. Having one of them off could cause erratic behavior.
    "</string>
    <string name="adding_contacts">"
        AutoResponder will only reply to Contacts you specify.

        You can import contacts from your Address Book, customize the responses, location and calendar requests, groups, and more!
    "</string>
    <string name="creating_groups">"
        Groups are collections of contacts, such as Friends, Family, and Coworkers.

        The same response and permissions can be set for all Contacts in this Group.

        Members can be added and removed, and a Contact may belong to only one Group.

        Deleting a Group WILL NOT delete a Contact associated with it.
    "</string>
    <string name="location_and_activity">"
        Contacts with set permissions may access your current location and calendar information.

        Location permissions are useful when a Contact wants to know "where are you?" and if you are driving, it will send them a link to show them!

        Calendar access allows Contacts to know "are you busy?", and if you have an event in you calendar, it will tell them!

        These can be completely turned OFF using the toggles on the main screen, and can be set on a per Contact/Group basis.
    "</string>
    <string name="universal_reply">"
        Universal Reply overrides all preset Contact/Group responses with a single message to everyone!

        This does not affect location and activity requests.

        This can be used by clicking the button on the main screen.
    </string>
    <string name="world_reply">"
        This switch, located in the settings, responds to ANY number! Not just the ones you list in your contacts!

        Any number can get a response, but if they are not a contact, they do not have permission to know your location or calendar info.
    "</string>
    <string name="time_limit_and_delay">"
        Time Limit sets how long AutoResponder will be activated, in the event you forget to turn it off later on. This time can be specified in Settings->Time Limit/Time Delay.

        Time Delay sets how long AutoResponder will wait before replying to the same Contact. This prevents spamming. This does not however override Location and Calendar requests.
    "</string>
    <string name="driving_detection">"
        Driving Detection automatically turns AutoResponder Off and On, based if the app knows you are driving or not.

        If you manually turn AutoResponder ON, it will stay on, even if you are not driving.

        This status is displayed in the Notification Drawer.
    "</string>
    <string name="parental_controls">"
        See Settings->Parental Controls for more information.

        This alerts the parent of a teen driver if the teen sent a text while they were driving! A major problem and road hazard.

        DISCLAIMER: THIS DOES NOT PREVENT TEXTING WHILE DRIVING, but allows alerts to the parent if the event occurs.
    "</string>
    <string name="response_log">"
        This is a history of all messages AutoResponder has sent out from the device.

        By clicking on a log, it expands showing more detail about the message sent.

        These logs can be cleared with the "Delete History" button.
    "</string>




</resources>